surfwithmoney.com 2013-04-20

# Surf With Money - get paid to surf, earn money daily online with autosurf, work at home paying free money liberty reserve, wiredpay, bitcoin, paypal, payza, egopay, moneybookers, okpay.

**Registration Data**

During registration, SurfWithMoney collects personal information including your name, email address. After providing SurfWithMoney with this information, you are no longer anonymous. You do not have to provide any personal information to use the SurfWithMoney service. In addition, we may not be able to provide you with some of the other services dependent upon the collection of such information, such as a personalized home page.

**SurfWithMoney Software Applications**

If you elect to install certain software products provided by SurfWithMoney to its users, SurfWithMoney may collect additional information about you. For example, we may allow bookmarks or personalized links that are accessible through SurfWithMoney. SurfWithMoney Software Products are spy-ware and ad-ware free. SurfWithMoney software products do not collect or report information about your activity on websites. SurfWithMoney software products include software that allow us to distribute updates and fixes, but such updates will occur only upon prior notice to you, except for the limited case where notice is not possible due to technical problems or an emergency that requires us to update the application in order to maintain existing functionality or to comply with the law. All such updates shall be governed by and made in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any applicable end user license agreements.

Information you provide when registering to receive goods or services from one or more of our partners. 

Information you provide when entering into a contest, sweepstakes or promotion sponsored by SurfWithMoney and/or one of our partners. 

Information you provide when filling out a user survey. 

Information you provide if you contact our customer service center. 

Data related to the areas of SurfWithMoney that you visit and how often you visit those areas. This includes co-branded sections of SurfWithMoney that are part of our overall service. 

Publicly available information that we obtain from third parties.

**How does SurfWithMoney use personal information?**

We use the personal information you supply us, including your registration data, to enhance the SurfWithMoney service, fulfill your requests for products, programs, or services, personalize your experience and provide you or permit others to provide you with special offers we think you will find valuable. We also use other information obtained from user site traffic patterns to better provide you with a personalized experience and special advertising offers and promotions. We view personalized advertising as beneficial to our users.

We also use your registration data information in connection with the SurfWithMoney Sweepstakes and other promotions in order to track your progress, to notify you if you are a winner and to ensure that we comply with the applicable laws.

SurfWithMoney uses the information described above to do, among other things, the following: 

We may also use the information we collect to develop summary reports for our advertisers. We provide this information to assist our advertisers in determining how to promote their products. We do not tell our advertisers who it was that saw or clicked on their advertisements unless you have specifically told us this is acceptable.

What choices are available to you regarding the collection, disclosure and distribution of personal information and how can you opt-out?

By maintaining a SurfWithMoney account you agree to share all rights to your personal information.

**What are cookies are and how they are used by SurfWithMoney?**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a web site"s computers and stored on your computer"s hard drive. As a standard practice, SurfWithMoney assigns a cookie with an anonymous identifier to each end user.

SurfWithMoney uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: 

Access your information when you "sign in," so that we can provide you with customized content, such as your profile and account options.

Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using SurfWithMoney.

Display relevant advertising banners based on your interests and activity on SurfWithMoney. 

Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.

Conduct research to improve SurfWithMoney"s content and services.

Require you to re-enter your SurfWithMoney password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

SurfWithMoney does not require users to accept cookies in order to enter or view the site or register. However, if you reject cookies, you will not be able to participate in using the SurfWithMoney members area, register, or to access other features. You can set your browser to reject cookies, or to notify you when SurfWithMoney or another company sends you a cookie. If you have questions about how to change your browser"s "cookie" settings, please contact the software manufacturer. Please note that some areas or features of SurfWithMoney will be significantly slower, or may not function at all, if cookies are disabled.

When you are on SurfWithMoney, advertisers and/or our partners may place their own cookies on your computer, even if you remain solely on the site site. SurfWithMoney does not control the use that these parties make of the information obtained through the cookies they send. If you have questions or concerns regarding cookies sent to you by companies other than SurfWithMoney, we encourage you to contact those companies directly.

**Who has access to your personally identifiable information?**

Your registration data is password-protected so that only you and SurfWithMoney have access to this personal information. You may edit your registration data by using your password.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. SurfWithMoney will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, if you share your computer or use a computer that is accessed by the general public (a university, library, etc...), remember to "log out" of your SurfWithMoney account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This will help to ensure that others cannot access your personal information.

SurfWithMoney takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you use these services at your own risk.

How and when is information disclosed to 3rd parties?

In general, SurfWithMoney may disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party.

In the event that all or substantially all of SurfWithMoney ownership and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, SurfWithMoney may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity.

**Sweepstakes, Promotions and Sponsorships:**

SurfWithMoney may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors of promotions or sweepstakes available through SurfWithMoney. Special sponsor promotions may often involve a request for information or a grant of permission to share personally identifiable information. By submitting this information or participating in the promotion, you give SurfWithMoney permission to transfer this information to the sponsor or as otherwise stipulated in connection with the rules or privacy policy applicable to the promotion. You should review any applicable sweepstakes and promotions rules or user agreement to see what is being shared. If personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will disclose this to you before we collect or transfer the data.

**Administering the Site and Compliance with Law:**

SurfWithMoney may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process. SurfWithMoney may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the public.

In addition, we may share your personal information under confidentiality agreements with certain third parties which assist us in developing, operating and maintaining SurfWithMoney or for determining whether or not to provide you with new services or special offers. Your registration data may be disclosed  at any time. SurfWithMoney also may disclose or access personally identifiable information for administrative and other purposes that we believe are necessary to develop, maintain and improve our products and services. This may include delivery services, fulfillment houses, and other similar entities.

**How can you correct inaccuracies in your personal information?**

You may update your personal information as necessary by going to the the profile page, which allows you to access and edit your registration account information given your account has been active for at least 30 days.

**What is SurfWithMoney"s policy regarding children"s privacy?**

SurfWithMoney is committed to the safety of our children. Children under 13 may not register or participate in the SurfWithMoney program. SurfWithMoney does not knowingly collect any personal information from such children at this site.
